飞马  车辆准备区
总统前往家乡巡回拉票备战南卡初选
邓巴下周二前往俄亥俄巡回拉票
约翰  我们雇你来洗车
John! We're paying you to clean cars,
不是让你来看报的
not read the paper.
好的  抱歉
Yeah, okay. Sorry.
纸牌屋
第四季  第三集
每当我感念慈爱的天主
When I think of the goodness of Jesus
和他对我的恩典
and all that He's done for me,
我的灵魂都会大喊  哈利路亚
my soul shouts out, "Hallelujah."
-哈利路亚  -阿门
- Hallelujah! - Amen.
真是太动人了
That was absolutely beautiful.
你们唱得好听又响亮
You sang it as heavenly and as loudly
不输我们达拉斯那边  阿门
as we do in Dallas. Amen!
阿门
Amen.
我母亲和我非常荣幸地
My mother and I are proud to
请出曾在国会为你们的权益奋战
introduce a man who fought for you in Congress.
如今继续在白宫为你们奋斗的人
He's fighting for you now in the White House.
我们希望能帮他留在白宫
We wanna help him to stay there.
-阿门  -阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
有请弗兰克·安德伍德总统
President Frank Underwood!
欢迎
All right!
谢谢
Thank you.
你们唱得太好了
You're all wonderful.
谢谢大家  快请坐
Thank you. Please be seated.
这样美好的上午  这样和谐的教堂
You know, it's on a morning like this, in a church like yours,
让我很骄傲能来到南卡罗莱纳
that I'm very proud to be a South Carolinian.
"你们有多少人开车来教堂的
"How many of you drove to church?
我先问各位一句
Let me start by asking,
今天早上你们有多少是开车来的"
how many of you drove to church here this morning?"
你们今天有多少人是开车来教堂的
How many of you drove to get to church here this morning?
你们有多少人是拼车来的呢
And how many of you drove together?
我理解拼车的各位
Well, I can appreciate that.
这年头的油价
Gas prices right now
快把大家都烧穷了
are putting a strain on everybody's pocketbooks.
你们说对不对
Isn't that true?
我想加夫尼的油价尤其高
I think maybe more here in Gaffney,
至少我对加夫尼尤其感同身受
at least I feel it here in Gaffney more than anywhere else.
"尤其是在加夫尼
"Especially here in Gaffney.
作为总统  我觉得对此负有责任
Now, as president, I feel responsible for that.
或许  在这里我的责任感更强烈
Or maybe, I feel even more so here.
我们这里向来就不怎么富裕
You know, we've never been a rich town.
我小的时候常常琢磨
You know, a lot of times in my childhood, I thought to myself,
'为什么我们这里在世人眼中就跟空气似的呢
'Why, we just, we were almost like an invisible town to people...
我们无关紧要'"
We didn't matter.'"
我们无关紧要
That we didn't matter.
当然了  我还是个白人小子呢
And, of course, I was a white boy.
虽然我家挺穷的
And as poor as my family was,
但还是比在座的许多家庭宽裕不少
we still were a lot better off than a lot of your families...
你们不仅要和贫穷斗争
who not only had to struggle through poverty
还得和种族歧视斗争
but had to fight racism as well.
你们有多少人还记得1973年
Now, how many of you remember 1973?
"你们有多少人还记得1973年
"Now, how many of you remember 1973?
那年的汽油价格跟今天一样飙涨
When gas prices were as bad as they are today,
我们为了加油  得排队排好几里地
and we had to wait hours just to fill our tank.
石油输出国家组织当时想要挟我们
Why, OPEC was trying to hold us hostage then
就像今天  俄罗斯也想故技重施
just as Russia's trying to hold us hostage now.
但是不知怎地
But somehow...
我们这个小社区团结了起来  是不是
our little community, why, we came together, didn't we?
我们团结了起来  是不是"  是的
We came together, didn't we?" Yes.
我们互帮互助  同舟共济
We looked out for each other. We were there for each other.
也许今天  我们对国内其他地方仍然无关紧要
Now, maybe we didn't matter to the rest of the country,
但我们对彼此却至关重要
but we sure as heck mattered to each other.
我们还在和贫穷斗争
We're still struggling with poverty,
我们仍然需要和种族歧视斗争
and racism is still something we have to fight against.
但是我知道  这地方非常重要
But I know that this town does matter.
你们都非常重要
That all of you matter.
我这么说可不仅仅是因为非裔
And I don't just say that because African Americans
手里握着全州一半的选票
represent half the vote in this state.
我这么说是因为  尽管有种种问题
I say that because, despite our troubles...
我们仍然团结在一起
we are one community.
我们仍然是一家人
One family.
这给了我们力量
And that gives us strength.
这股力量无比强大
That strength is a powerful thing.
不容忽视
It's not invisible.
光芒万丈
It radiates.
我相信上帝会给我目标
I place my faith in God to give me purpose.
我希望你们给我力量
I put my hope in you to give me strength.
嗯  先生
Yes, sir.
而明天你们投票的时候
And come tomorrow, when you vote...
我也希望你们能信任我
I hope that you will place your trust in me...
让我们继续带领这个国家前行
...to help continue to lead this country
就像我们在这里齐心协力  共建家园
as we have led this community, together.
非常感谢你们
Thank you all very much.
早上好
Good morning.
我是莉安·哈维  去华盛顿
I'm LeAnn Harvey, traveling to Washington.
第一夫人还没来  哈维女士
The First Lady isn't here yet, Ms. Harvey,
不过如果你愿意的话可以先登机
but you're welcome to board the plane, if you'd like.
不了  我还是等她来吧  谢谢
Uh, no, I'll wait until she gets here. Thank you.
艾丹
Aidan.
我刚把调研报告发过去了
Hey, I just sent the research.
-结果怎么样  -遮天怒火啊
- What's the gist? - The anger, it's biblical.
-油价闹的吗  -是啊  上学烧汽油
- Uh, gas prices? - Yeah, gas is school.
上班烧汽油
Gas is work.
全家去迪士尼乐园也得烧汽油
Gas is the family trip to Disneyland.
油价每涨一毛钱  愤怒指数就涨6个百分点
Every cent it goes up is another six points on the anger index.
我们预测油价到了7元  就会全民暴动
We predict that $7 a gallon will get you riots.
第一夫人呢
What about the First Lady?
她的形象比她丈夫积极多了
Oh, she's faring better than he is.
主要是同情她母亲病重
Sympathy for the sick mother.
多谢你们加急赶出来
Thanks for the rush job on this.
你是朋友嘛  再说这个要比
Well, you're a friend. And this is far more interesting than...
调查五岁小孩的抗抑郁药名  或者
testing names of anti-depressants for five-year-olds, or...
中产家庭主妇垂涎什么颜色的跑步机有趣多了
what color cross trainers soccer moms will drool over.
-我还以为你讨厌政治  -没错
- I thought you hated politics. - I do.
但是愤怒和诱惑
But anger? And seduction?
这些可好玩得很
Those are interesting.
-母亲  我的耳环  -什么
- Mother, my earrings. - Yes?
被你拿了
You took them.
我才没拿
I did no such thing.
我说了不是我...
I said I don't...
你要拿我的钱  我也得拿你点东西
You're taking my money. I took something of yours.
克莱尔
Claire...
你今天走了就别回来了
When you leave today, I don't want you coming back.
我想来就来  想走就走  母亲
Oh, I'll come and go as I please, Mother.
太滑稽了
This is unreal.
你确定我们能指望这人
You sure we can count on this guy?
他厌恶弗兰西斯  这一点绝对可以指望
He loathes Francis. That we can count on.
但是你也多留意
But use your best judgment.
这是谁做的调查
Who compiled this?
和我有合作的一家分析公司
An analytics firm I contract with,
国内顶尖
one of the best in the country.
他们可靠吗
They can be trusted?
可靠  我直接和老板合作的
Yes. I work directly with the owner.
弗兰西斯非常希望能拿下南卡罗莱纳
Francis really needs this win in South Carolina.
当然了
He sure does.
再向市场投放些战略储备吧
Let's release more of the strategic reserve.
这也许能减缓涨价势头  但遏制不住的
That might slow down the price inflation, but it won't halt it.
两位女士可喜欢这道肋排啊
How are you two ladies enjoying those ribs?
吃完饭之后我得美美地睡一会儿
Mmm, I'm gonna need a nap after this.
那你们慢用
Well, you'll have time.
我还得打两小时的电话筹款
I have two hours of fundraising calls to make.
非常感谢您
It was very nice of you
让我们在您家落脚  总统先生
to let us stay at your house, Mr. President.
我们加夫尼人就是这么好客
Well, that's how we do things here in Gaffney.
先生
Sir?
听着  我绝不会和他谈救市问题
Listen, I am not gonna negotiate a bailout
除非他在私有化问题上让步
if he won't budge on privatization.
他想饿死自己的人民  随他的便
If he wants to let his own people starve, so be it.
他或许会转向北京求助  那样就会
He may look for relief from Beijing, and that would--
他恨中国胜过恨我们
The only thing he hates more than us is China.
他不会对北京扣头的
He won't kowtow.
但如果佩特罗夫真的向北京低头
But if Petrov does cave to them,
那全球能源市场就会...
that puts the global energy--
凯茜  我待会儿再打给你
Look, Cathy, I have to call you back.
-什么时候  -半小时前吧
- When? - About 30 minutes ago.
-这是您的保险柜  433号  -谢谢
- So this will be your box, number 433. - Thank you.
您要不再在我们这里再开个储蓄账户
Would you like to open up a savings account with us?
-借记卡什么的  -不了  保险箱就好
- Debit card? - No, the box is fine.
好吧
Okay.
我能不能自己...
Would you mind if I...
当然可以  我回避一下
Oh, sure. I'll give you some privacy.
谢谢啦
Thank you.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
我也是  弗兰西斯
You, too, Francis.
真没想到
I'm surprised.
一直没你的消息  然后你突然就来了
I don't hear from you, then you just show up.
说实话  直到飞机落地  我都不确定要不要来
Mmm, to be honest, I wasn't sure until I landed.
你有点晒黑了
You've gotten some sun.
昨天去田间地头拉票来着  该戴顶帽子的
Tractor-pulling event yesterday. I should've worn a hat.
-桃瑞丝和西莉娅也在吗  -来过
- Are Doris and Celia here? - They were.
我在客房里为她们加了两张床
I set up cots for them in the guest room,
但我一听你要来  就让她们住酒店去了
but when I heard you were coming, I sent them off to a hotel.
我想着你可能会想住客房
I figured you'd want that room for yourself.
多谢你费心了
That's very thoughtful.
你马上还有活动吧
You have an event now.
莱姆斯顿学院
Limestone College.
那我和你一起去
Well, I'll join you.
她们也会去  如果你不想见...
They'll be there, if you'd rather not see--
没事
It'll be fine.
除非你不想让我去
Unless you'd rather I not go.
怎么会  我很乐意你一起去
No, I'd love you to come.
如果他知道我搀和进来
If he knows I'm involved...
那就别让他知道
So make sure he doesn't.
我能看看吗
Can I see it?
我的天
Oh, boy.
这下有好戏看了
Now, this could get interesting.
明早之前办好
We need it done by tomorrow morning.
我表亲有个朋友  开了家工业打印店
Well, my cousin has a friend, owns an industrial print shop,
但这么大幅的
but a job that size...
这些应该够了
This should cover it.
绰绰有余
And then some.
想不到希瑟·邓巴也会玩这一套
Oh, I didn't know Heather Dunbar had it in her.
认识你很高兴  蔡斯先生
It's nice to meet you, Mr. Chase.
真不喝点冰茶吗
Well, are you sure you wouldn't like some iced tea?
谢谢  不喝了  我还有事
Thank you, no. I should get going.
扭得这么好看  要不来点薯条吧
How about some fries with that shake?
照我说的把事情办好  别让我再跑一趟了
Get done what I want done. Don't make me come back here.
-曼尼怎么说的  -我代你的班  哥们
- What did Manny say? - I got your shift, bro.
-那车呢  -那辆蒙迪欧
- What about the car? - The Fusion.
我可以重设里程表
I can reset the odometer,
下班之后停到你家门口
park it in front of your place after work.
不过  你明晚之前必须还回来
But, hey... you gotta get it back by tomorrow night.
-不然等他们清点库存...  -我保证
- Otherwise, when they do the inventory-- - I promise you.
好吧
All right.
说说报酬吧
So the cost.
等我工资发下来我就...
As soon as I get my paycheck, I'll--
不  我不想要钱
No. I don't want money.
其他在这干活儿的人我都看不上眼
Most of the other guys work here, they ain't much to look at.
但你
You?
我怎么都看不够
Keep lookin' over.
哥们  你别...
Hey, man, listen...
-你还想不想用车  -我自己想办法吧
- You want the car or not? - I'll find some other way.
我知道你的底细
I know about you.
我见过你的假释官来查你的岗
I seen your parole officer come check in on you.
如果他知道你偷了一辆车  会怎么办你
What would he say about you taking one of these cars?
来吧
Come on.
上车
Get in.
我今天刚刚了解到  莱姆斯顿学院
I just learned today that Limestone College,
创立于1845年
founded in 1845,
是南卡罗莱纳第一所招收女生的学校
was the first women's college in South Carolina,
在全国也是最早的几所
and one of the first in the nation.
这非常了不起
And that's something to be proud of.
自那时起  这所学校和她的学生成就斐然
And since then, this school and its students have flourished.
这个年轻向上的群体
A young, eager community
超越种族  性别和背景
of men and women of all races and backgrounds,
是美国未来的最佳写照
a true reflection of America's future.
他是怎么说服你回来的
How did he convince you to come back?
我自己说服了自己
I convinced myself.
我丈夫去世时我们结婚已有46年
Forty-six years I was married to my husband before he passed.
但如果他像弗兰克对你那样对我
But if he'd pulled on me what Frank pulled on you,
他会早死很多年
he would've been long gone.
我认为这样对大家都有好处
I think it's worked out for the best.
您女儿将会是一位出色的众议员
Your daughter is going to make a fabulous congresswoman.
谢谢
Well, thank you.
还有两分钟
Two minutes.
弗兰克·安德伍德了解我们对平等的渴求
Now, Frank Underwood understands the need for equality,
无论是教育平等  还是生活中的平等
in education and throughout our lives.
最重要的是  他相信给每个美国人
Most of all, he believes in giving every American
谋生计的机会
the opportunity to earn a living.
他以前就践行了这一信念  他也会坚持下去
He put this belief into action before and he will again,
弗兰克·安德伍德
and Frank Underwood
决不会允许他的奋斗止步于莱姆斯顿
will not allow this journey to end with Limestone.
你们将步入世界
You will go out into this world
让世人惊艳于你们的才智
and astonish us all with your intellect,
你们的价值  和你们的力量
your... your worthiness, and your strength.
现在请允许我请出我见过的最坚强的女人
Now, I would like to introduce two of the strongest women I know.
你们俩真是  亲密无间啊
Well, don't you look thick as thieves.
以及美国的第一夫人  克莱尔·安德伍德
...and the First Lady of the United States, Claire Underwood.
就好像她从没离开过
It's as though she never left.
我担心的就是这个
And that's what I'm afraid of.
来吧  我们尽快干完
All right, let's hurry on up, now.
布加耶夫告诉我他们愿意
Bugayev is telling me that they are willing
在下月1日之前
to reduce their oil output by
再减产20%的原油
another 20% by the first of next month.
油价走势预测如何
What are the projections on gas prices?
每桶原油超过150美元
North of 150 a barrel for oil.
汽油每加仑6到7块
Six, maybe $7 a gallon for fuel.
我的电话都快被打爆了  先生
My phone has been ringing off the hook, sir,
从英国到波兰都打个不停
from the U.K. to Poland.
国际货币基金组织希望
The IMF wants to help us
帮助我们制定债务免除方案
with the debt relief solution.
先生
Sir?
我们得以暴制暴
We need to respond to strength with strength.
我不知道我们还要怎么"暴"
Well, I don't know how we could be any stronger,
除非入侵俄国
other than to invade Russia.
如果我们那么做了呢
And what if we do?
-什么  先生  -不是动用军队
- Excuse me, sir? - Not with troops.
而是用恐惧
With fear.
他从未信任过我们
He's never trusted us.
他已经觉得我们操纵了米尔金失败的政变
He already thinks we're behind Milkin's failed coup.
如果我们让米尔金有机会取得成功呢
What if we put Milkin in a position to succeed.
我并不在乎米尔金是不是真能成功
Now, I don't care if Milkin actually succeeds.
结冻他一切财产  让他飞去接壤国家
Unfreeze all his assets. Fly him to a border country.
让他跟其他异见者见面
Put him in a room with other dissidents.
得让佩特罗夫知道我们不会罢休
Petrov needs to know that we'll stop at nothing.
先生  这样的行为将造成外交影响...
Sir, the diplomatic repercussions of such an action--
我只想装装样子
All I want is the appearance.
尽快估计一下最好和最坏的结果
Let's look at best and worst case scenarios as soon as possible.
多谢了
Thank you very much.
抱歉  我以为
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought you were--
那床太硬了
That bed was too stiff.
-那我过去睡吧  -就睡这儿吧
- I'll sleep in there then. - Sleep in here.
我们以前在地板上铺床垫
We had the mattress on the floor.
什么
What?
头一年  床垫还有邦邦硬的枕头
That first year, the mattress and those lumpy pillows.
你大半夜还老偷我的
Which you used to steal from me in the middle of the night.
还不是因为你把被子都拽走了
Well, because you would hog all the covers.
天呐  我们当时过得真够差的
God, we were living like heathens.
那是因为我们把一切都投入了竞选
Well, because we were spending everything we had on the race.
但我记得我以前把这里想作宫殿
I remember I used to think this place was a palace, though.
-这里是座宫殿  -跟农场没法比
- It was. - Not compared to the ranch.
是座宫殿  是因为它属于我们
Well, it was a palace because it was ours.
晚安  弗兰西斯
Good night, Francis.
安德伍德2016
媒体都包围了房子
The press has surrounded the house.
我根本出不去
I can't leave the damn place
得先想好我究竟该说什么
until I know exactly what I'm gonna say.
我们得取消您的活动
We need to cancel your events.
当然得取消了
Of course we need to cancel my events.
-我脸上的表情...  -怎么回事
- The expression on my face is a-- - What's going on?
...拍摄地点未知
...taken in a nondescript location,
似乎并非是直接对三K党的支持
does not seem to be a direct endorsement for the KKK.
-天呐  -我父亲
- My God. - My father.
先生  琼斯议员女士要回德州了
Sir? Congresswoman Jones is heading back to Texas.
马上给我接通她的电话
Get her on the phone for me, right now.
密查姆  你得去帮我个忙
Meechum, I need you to do me a favor.
现在尚不清楚
There are no clues at the moment
此事是谁所为
as to who may be responsible,
损坏公物行为将安德伍德与三K党联系了起来  南卡罗来纳州  加夫尼
加夫尼警察正在取下照片
but Gaffney PD is taking the canvas picture down
一小时内就能完成  以备进一步调查
within the hour for further examination.
就在初选这天
On primary day.
我现在无法证实任何事  那是谁
I can't verify anything yet in terms of who it is,
或者照片是否是真
or even whether it's real, or--
新罕布什尔州前一天  是婚姻问题的报道
The day before New Hampshire, there's a marriage story,
现在在南卡罗来纳州又闹这事
and now in South Carolina we have this?
我们为什么会遭偷袭
Uh, how are we getting blindsided?
-我该接一下  -让它响去吧
- I should get that-- - Let it ring.
听着
Look...
吵架的事还是你告诉我我才知道
I didn't even know about the fight until you told me.
你怎么能指望我知道照片的事
And how was I supposed to know about this photo?
因为预防这种烂事就是你的职责
Because it is your job to get out ahead of this shit.
这事该是对手研究团队去挖  竞选就是如此
The oppo team should've tracked this down. That's the campaign.
如果沃恩不知道  或是如果总统没告诉他
So, if Vaughn didn't know, or the president didn't tell him...
肯定是他身边的人  能掌握很多情况的人
It has to be somebody close to him. Someone with a lot of access.
总统打来了
The president's on the line.
先生  是道格  赛斯也在
Sir, it's Doug. I'm in here with Seth.
我要说实话  我要说那是我父亲
I'm gonna tell the truth. I'm gonna say it is my father.
如果能说得好
That's probably the best response,
这样回应或许最好
if you have a good way to frame it.
我知道该说什么  问题是在哪说
I know what to say. The question is where.
一对一  独家采访
One-on-one. Something exclusive.
不能跟媒体说
Not in front of the media.
我得直接对选民说
I need to connect directly to the voters,
非裔选民
the African American voters.
总统先生  国务卿打来了
Mr. President, I've got the Secretary of State.
我回头再打过去
I'll call her back.
稍等  密查姆
Hang on, boys. Meechum?
还在这儿  先生
It's here, sir.
你都了解到了什么
What can you tell me?
昨天  一个叫莱斯利·麦金泰尔的女人
Yesterday, a woman named Leslie McIntyre
开了个新保险箱
opened a new box.
我正在查这个名字
I'm having the name run now,
但她似乎用了假社保号
but it looks like she used a fake social.
监控录像呢
What about security footage?
他们每天早上重置摄像头
They reset the cameras every morning.
我问了她长什么样
I asked what she looked like
经理只说是个白人黑发女人
and all the manager said is that it was a Caucasian brunette.
没什么异常之处
Nothing strange about her.
好吧  把盒子拿回来
All right. Bring the box back here.
一刻别让它离开你的视线范围
Don't let it out of your sight.
就我所知  只有一张照片
As far as I know, there's only one photograph.
密查姆说照片还在银行
Meechum says it's still at the bank.
先生  是我一个人了
Sir, it's just me.
你跟我想到一起了吗
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
你盯住他
Well, you keep an eye on him.
我要白宫所有人的邮件和电话记录
I want emails and phone records of everyone in the White House.
包括你的
Including yours.
我的  你真觉得...
Mine? You honestly think--
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?
没有
No.
很好
Good.
真是不幸
It's unfortunate.
邓巴女士  邓巴女士
Ms. Dunbar! Ms. Dunbar? Ms. Dunbar?
邓巴对"安德伍德2016"照片做出回应
这样的画面
The imagery...
居然有人靠如此卑劣的手段
That anyone would try to inflame racial discord
企图煽动种族不和
by doing something so base.
那是不是凯文·安德伍德根本不重要
Whether it's Calvin Underwood isn't the point.
即便是  这一点我们无法确认
If it is, and we have no confirmation on that,
那么是谁挂上去的  为什么要这么做
I mean... Who put this up? And why?
邓巴对"安德伍德2016"照片做出回应
谁知道呢
Who knows.
而且父亲的罪未必是孩子的罪
And the sins of the father aren't necessarily the sins of the son.
但  这令人不安  十分不安
But... it's troubling. Very troubling.
这样的伎俩很可能揭开旧疮疤
Stunts like these have the potential to open old wounds.
我们不能允许那样的事发生  我们得不受其影响
We can't let that happen. We need to rise above it.
要明白  不管你支持谁
Make clear, no matter who you support,
这样的行为是不可容忍的
that this sort of behavior will not be tolerated.
给我接克拉克牧师和吉恩·克兰希
Get me Reverend Clark and Gene Clancy on the phone.
他们要你去大巴那边
Hey, they want you out by the bus.
大巴那边
By the bus?
-你是谁  -抱歉
- Um, who are you? - Sorry.
巴特勒县办公室的马克
Mark from the Butler County office.
他们要辛辛那提的志愿者
They want all the Cincinnati volunteers
去大巴那边集合跟邓巴合影
to gather by the bus for a photo with Dunbar.
珍告诉我我不能离开岗位的
Jenn told me I wasn't supposed to leave--
所以她叫我过来喊你
That's why she sent me.
她不希望你错过合影  去吧
She didn't want you to miss the photo. Go.
大巴那边吗
Out by the bus?
她叫我替你
She told me to cover for you.
好
Okay, um...
有几个人没来
well, there were a couple of no-shows,
其他人都来了
but, you know, otherwise, everyone's here.
-好  谢谢  -太棒了  谢谢
- Okay. Thanks. - Very convenient. Thanks.
快去吧
Enjoy.
我是《克利夫兰老实人报》的戴维·格里姆斯
I'm David Grimes with the Cleveland Plain Dealer.
你的证件呢
Where's your credential?
我蠢得把证件忘在车里了
I was an idiot and left it in the car.
不过前台签到处的人认识我
They recognized me at the check-in desk, though.
我可以带你去等候处
I can direct you to the bullpen,
但是这一区不对媒体开放
but this area is off-limits to the press.
我其实是来采访辛西娅·德里斯科尔的
I'm actually supposed to do an interview with Cynthia Driscoll.
先遣人员叫我来这边
The Advance guys said I should come this way.
在这里等一下
Wait here.
抱歉  总统先生  我们做不到
I'm sorry, Mr. President, we just can't do it.
这里45%的选票在非裔手中
Forty-five percent of the vote here is African American.
你和你母亲对我的支持
You and your mother standing by my side
会有很重要的作用...
would go a long way to put this--
我在一个非裔及拉丁裔的选区竞选议员
I am running for Congress in a black and Latino district.
我母亲曾在游行时被暴打  被水冲
My mother was beaten and hosed down in marches.
你想让我们替一个三K党人的儿子作担保吗
You want us to vouch for a man whose father was in the KKK?
-不  他不是三K党  -照片上那个就是他
- No, he was not in the Klan. - That was him in that picture.
对  可这个我已经解释过了
Yes, but I've explained that.
内战就是在本州掀起的
This is the state where the Civil War started,
有些人汽车保险杠上还贴着南军旗贴纸
where you can still see rebel flags on bumper stickers.
这里曾有很严重的种族暴行  总统先生
There is a history of racist brutality here, Mr. President.
那种形象影响很大
Those sort of symbols matter.
能让你母亲接电话吗
Could you put your mother on, please?
妈妈
Mom?
他想跟你说话
He wants to speak to you.
总统先生
Mr. President.
听着  我们需要团结  我替西莉娅背书了
Listen, we need to stand together. Now, I've endorsed Celia.
克莱尔在德州能给她帮很大忙
Claire can do a great deal for her in Texas.
现在远离安德伍德一家对她更好
She's better off without the Underwoods at this point.
那你的诊所呢
But what about your clinic?
你要是拿我们的诊所要挟我  别人会怎么看
Imagine how that would look, holding our clinic for ransom.
我是想博取您的友好  议员女士
I'm appealing to your goodwill, Congresswoman.
等我们不再遭受殴打和枪击
When we stop getting beaten and shot...
我就会对您友好的  总统先生
you'll have my goodwill, Mr. President.
再见
Goodbye.
再接吉恩·克兰希
Get me Gene Clancy again.
会不会是奥林·蔡斯  弗兰西斯
What if it's Oren Chase, Francis?
他也可能拿到一份副本
He could've gotten his hands on a copy.
照片可能不止一张
There may be more than one.
先打给密查姆  然后克兰希
Meechum first, then Clancy.
卢卡斯
Lucas?
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
-我还以为你...  -是的  不过已经出来了
- I thought you were--  - I was. I'm... I'm out now.
这很重要
This is important.
总统先生  您父亲是种族主义者吗
Mr. President, was your father a racist?
您父亲是种族主义者吗
Was your father a racist?
安德伍德太夫人  你母亲还好吗
Mrs. Underwood, is your mother okay?
总统先生
Mr. President!
-蔡斯先生  -你是谁
- Mr. Chase? - Who are you?
特勤局的
United States Secret Service.
我们要的不是你  蔡斯先生
We're not after you, Mr. Chase.
我们是想要指使你这么干的人
We're after whoever put you up to it.
指使我做什么
Put me up to what?
你可以现在回答我
You can answer me here,
或者我们可以去问哥伦比亚办事处
or we can go to the Columbia field office for questioning.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
请您跟我来一下  先生
All right, I need you to come with me, sir.
-等等  -请出来  先生
- Now, hold on. - Step outside, sir.
我要找律师
I wanna talk to a lawyer.
4126号需要支援
I need backup at 4126.
-没必要这样吧  -除非你合作
- Come on, that's not necessary. - Not if you cooperate, sir.
跟你说不会惹麻烦吧
If I talk to you, I won't get in trouble?
我向上帝起誓  邓巴女士  这都是真的
I swear to God, Ms. Dunbar. It's all true.
证据呢
Then where's the proof?
我没办法找证据  但你可以
I don't have the means, but you do.
你调查过他  你知道他很危险
You've investigated him before. You know he's dangerous.
古德温先生
Mr. Goodwin--
如果我不是查到了真相  他为什么要针对我
Why would he go after me if I wasn't onto something?
这是一起高级钓鱼执法
This was a high-level sting operation.
还为此调动了大量资源
Major resources were dedicated to it.
我原本是个记者  没有犯罪记录
I'm... I was a journalist, no criminal record.
怎么突然就成了威胁  除非我...
How am I suddenly such a threat, unless I'm--
就算我相信你
Even if I did believe you,
我已经不是司法部的了  现在只是个普通市民
I am no longer part of the DOJ. I am a private citizen now.
正在竞选总统
Who's running for president--
你来这儿不违反证人保护计划的规定吗
Aren't you breaking WITSEC protocol by being here?
我不想再跟他谈了
I am no longer comfortable with this.
你是我最后的机会  求你了
You're... you're my last chance. Please!
-我建议你还是回家吧  -我  可是我
- I suggest that you go back home. - I'm... The things I've--
-别逼我们叫保安  -求你了  就
- Don't make us get security involved.  - Please. Just--
你得在这儿等五分钟  让她离开
Just give us five minutes until she's out of the building.
求你了  求你听我说
Please. Please listen to me.
我求你了
I'm... I'm begging you.
帮帮我
Just help me...
Help.
求你了  求你了
Please, please...
天呐
Oh, God...
你怎么能带他来见我
How could you put me in a room with him?
我并不知道他想要说什么
I didn't know what he was gonna say.
不过我以为他这么煞费苦心
But I assumed that if he went to such great lengths--
他只有酒驾的证据  那什么都不算上
The DUI, that's all he has proof of. That's nothing.
我都帮过别人逃脱酒驾的惩罚
Even I have helped people get off for that.
-还有外遇  -没证据
- There's the affair... - With no evidence.
他又在那扯什么谋杀  还杀了两个
Then he leaps to murder... Two murders?
这人有病
The man is troubled.
他那眼神我们都看见了
We saw the look in his eye.
我以为他有什么真凭实据呢
I thought he might have something real.
他以前做编辑做得挺好的
He used to be a good editor.
可他现在是个定了罪的重犯
And now he is a convicted felon.
你说的要不遗余力
You said no stone unturned.
对不起  我应该想得更周到一些的
I'm sorry, I should have thought better of it.
是啊  你是应该
Yes, you should have.
就这样吧  我们在南卡罗来纳情况如何
Let's let it go. How are we doing in South Carolina?
早期民调结果不错
Early exit polls are good.
-我们有机会赢  -真能赢吗
- We have a shot at winning. - Actually winning?
那个广告牌造成了不小的破坏
That billboard's done real damage.
你能这么做我很感激  吉恩
I appreciate you doing this, Gene.
你真是救了我一命
You're really saving my life here.
等我竞选县长的时候你记着就行
Just remember it when I run for county executive.
你随时需要我随时过来
I'll be down here whenever you need me.
重点不在时间  而是给什么和给多少
Oh, it's not the when, it's the what. And how much.
下午好  奥林
Afternoon, Oren.
-总统先生  -坐吧
- Mr. President. - Have a seat.
上次大桃子的事儿你还没长记性啊
Didn't you learn your lesson with all that Peachoid nonsense?
你说了要帮我搞定第4选区的
Well, you promised to help me with the 4th.
我被怨恨蒙蔽了
I let my bitterness get the better of me.
谁找的你  一个女的吗
Who specifically approached you? A woman?
-黑头发  -对
- Brunette?  - Yeah.
大概这么高  挺好看的
Uh, about so tall, good-looking.
也不告诉我名字
Wouldn't give me her name.
我们应该把所有的
We should get photos
邓巴团队里符合描述的人的照片找来
of everyone in Dunbar's staff that fits that description.
已经在整理了  夫人
Already compiling it, ma'am.
至于你嘛
And as for you...
你要去上电视  越多越好
you're gonna plant yourself in front of as many TV cameras
愿意拍你的都去上
that can gather around that bony ass of yours.
你要表现出被罪恶感折磨  然后良心发现
You're gonna be wracked with guilt and overcome with conscience.
你做好了  我就确保你不会被起诉
And you do that and I'll make sure that you aren't charged.
你想让我说是邓巴指使的吗
You want me to say it was Dunbar?
拜托  聪明点  奥林  她会告你诽谤的
Come on, be smarter than that, Oren. She'll sue you for slander.
就说你被收买了就行
Just say you were bought
剩下的大家自己就能琢磨出来
and people will connect the dots on their own.
把他带走吧
Get him out of here.
我希望你不会像
I hope you don't Welsh on
对待奥林一样违背对我的诺言
your promise to me the way you did with Oren.
你是家人  吉恩  我绝不会背叛家人
You're family, Gene. I would never betray one of the family.
走吧
Shall we?
准备好了吗
Ready?
你们很多人曾选我当市长
Many of you voted for me for mayor
是因为你们认识我一辈子了
because you've known me your whole lives.
而我认识弗兰克·安德伍德一辈子了
Well, I've known Frank Underwood my whole life.
他是我的朋友  我信任他
He's my friend and I trust him,
我也不在乎那个广告牌上到底是什么
and I don't care what's on that billboard.
我为他是我的总统感到自豪
I'm proud he's my president,
我也为今天能同他站在一起而自豪
and I'm proud to have... be standing with him here today.
谢谢  吉恩
Thank you, Gene.
昨天  我站在这个教堂里
Yesterday, I stood in this church...
我提到了我们这个群体
and I talked about community.
我提到了我们集体的力量
I talked about our collective strength,
无论是黑人还是白人  在危机时刻走到一起
black and white, coming together during times of crisis.
今天肯定有很多人觉得我是个伪君子
And today there's probably a lot of you who think I'm a hypocrite.
一个父亲是三K党的人  怎么可能站在这里
How can a man whose father was in the KKK stand up here
真心实意地说出那些话呢
and mean the things he said?
没错  照片上的人是我父亲
Yes, that is my father in that photograph,
我不会否认
I'm not going to deny it.
但事实是  他不是三K党的人
But the truth is he wasn't in the Klan.
拍照片的那年
The year that photo was taken,
我父亲需要五千美元偿还债务
my father needed $5,000 to pay off our debts,
不然银行就会没收我们的农场
or the bank was gonna foreclose on our farm.
父亲跑遍了这附近
Now, my father went to every other bank
方圆百里内的所有银行
within a hundred miles of here,
没一个愿意贷款给他
and no one would give him a loan.
他向朋友去借  挨家挨户地问
He asked friends, he asked family,
没人有那么多钱
but nobody had that kind of money.
我们马上就要倾家荡产了
And we were about to lose everything.
当时  加夫尼第一银行的行长
Now, at the time, the owner of the Gaffney First Bank
是三K党的成员
was a member of the Klan.
这在座的一些人知道
Some of you know that.
他完全听从三K党的指挥
And he would do whatever the Klan told him to do,
我父亲也清楚这一点
and my father knew that.
所以父亲就做了他不得不做的
So my father did what he had to do.
他参加了一次会议并乞求那个分会的领导
He went to a meeting and begged the leader of that chapter
在银行行长面前说句话
to talk to the owner of the bank.
照片就是拍摄于那次会议
And at that meeting, that's when that photograph was taken.
他出现在那里仅仅是为了挽救我们的农场
The only reason he was there was to try to save our farm.
凯文·安德伍德痛恨自己参加了那次会议
Now, Calvin Underwood hated himself for going to that meeting.
也痛恨自己拍下了那张照片
He hated himself for taking that photograph.
但如果不能保住我们的农场  他会更痛恨自己
But he would've hated himself even more if he'd lost our farm...
如果他不能养活自己的家人
if he hadn't been able to provide and support his family.
我不会试着让你们原谅他
Now, look, I'm not trying to ask you to forgive him
出现在那张照片中
being in that photograph.
他大概以为永远不会有人看到这照片
He probably thought no one would ever see it.
但我恳请大家同情他的困境
But I am asking you to empathize with his predicament.
并扪心自问...
And ask yourselves...
你们会为挽救自己的家庭做些什么
what would you do to save your family?
那盗取了照片  破坏了广告牌的人
Now, whoever stole that photograph and vandalized that billboard,
他们的目的不是要揭露关于我过去的重大丑闻
they're not trying to unearth some big scandal about my past,
因为真相并非如此
'cause it just isn't true.
他们的目的是让我们分裂
What they're trying to do is divide us.
他们真正要达到的目的
What they really wanna succeed in doing
是确保大家今天不把票投给我
is making sure you don't vote for me today.
他们为玷污我的形象
They've gone to a whole
真是煞费苦心
lot of trouble to make me look pretty bad.
但这就是政治
But that's politics.
我今天来到这里
My hope in coming here today...
开诚布公地对这件事发表声明  是希望
and speaking openly and honestly about this...
我们能够保持团结
is that we can stay united.
因此我打算一直待在这里
So my plan is to stay here as long as it takes,
跟每一个人单独谈谈
to speak to each one of you individually,
解答你们所有的疑问
and answer every question that you might have.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
非常感谢  女士
Thank you very much, ma'am.
安德伍德总统
President Underwood,
在他家乡南卡罗来纳州加夫尼发表现场讲话
speaking live in his home town of Gaffney, South Carolina,
总统对三K党公告牌一事作出回应
回应称其父
addressing claims that
是三K党成员的言论
his father was a member of the Ku Klux Klan.
昨晚当地一块公告牌遭到破坏
A billboard there was vandalized late last night
被挂上了一张总统父亲站在一名
with a photo of his father standing
身着三K党长袍的男子旁边的照片
next to a man in Klan robes
并配文  "安德伍德2016"
with the caption, "Underwood 2016."
正如我们刚刚所看到的  总统没有否认
As we've just seen, the president did not deny allegations
总统对三K党公告牌一事作出回应
其父亲与该组织有联系的指控
that his father had some connection to the organization,
反而解释说凯文·安德伍德只参加了一次会议
instead explaining that Calvin Underwood attended one meeting
是为了
as a last resort
避免家里的桃园不被没收  不得已而为之
to save his family's peach farm from foreclosure.
今早其家人被指与三K党有关联的
The president was subject to widespread criticism
消息一经传出
after news of his family's
总统便饱受批评
alleged Klan connection broke this morning.
今天的初选结果将会...
Today's primary result will show--
我不知道她的名字  我问过  但她没说
I don't know her name. I asked, but she wouldn't tell me.
奥林·蔡斯承认破坏广告牌
我深感抱歉
And I deeply regret
让我的政治倾向影响到了判断力
that I allowed my political leanings to compromise my better judgment.
我想对可能侵犯到的人道歉
I want to apologize to anyone I might have offended
抱歉翻出了如此痛苦的画面
by hoisting up such painful imagery.
有人打电话问是不是我们做的
We're getting calls asking if it was us.
-你觉得是我们团队的人吗  -绝对不会
- Do you think someone from our team-- - Absolutely not.
我觉得是安德伍德叫他这么说的
I think Underwood put this guy up to it.
他想反过来陷害我们
He's trying to turn this back around on us.
我们必须坚决否认
We need to deny, forcefully.
我已经在下一场活动安排了媒体采访
I'm already putting a press avail together at your next event.
可能我们得再考虑一下古德温了
Maybe we need to reconsider Goodwin.
-你怎么想的  -我也不确定
- What do you have in mind? - I'm not sure.
看这个
Look at this.
是从白宫泄露的
It came from the goddamn White House!
我们在讯问摄影师了  先生
We're questioning the photographer now, sir.
我准备好了声明
I've got a statement prepared that
这只是个普通活动
this was a run-of-the-mill event,
您和许多参与内战重演的演员合过影
that you took photos with lots of re-enactors.
你怎么解释都没用
It doesn't matter how you spin it.
我刚刚在教堂
I just stood in front of
面对一群非裔美国人
a group of African Americans in a church
请他们相信我
asking them to believe in me.
他们看到我父亲和三K党人并立已够糟了
It's bad enough they see my father next to a Klansman.
现在又看到我和奴隶制的象征站在一起
Now they see me next to a symbol of slavery.
我要查出是谁泄露的
I wanna find out who's leaking this shit,
把他的头钉在木桩上
and I want their head on a goddamn stake!
先生  我有个想法
Sir, I have a theory.
我觉得...
I think...
我觉得可能是艾德华·密查姆
Well, I think it might be Edward Meechum.
密查姆
Meechum?
他知道您和第一夫人发生了争吵
He knew about the argument between you and the First Lady.
弗吉尼亚那次他也跟去了
He was there on that trip to Virginia.
他绝不会做出这种事来
He would never do something like this.
邓巴有很多钱
Dunbar has a lot of money.
向各大电视台发布声明
Put out a statement to the networks
我不会发表落选演讲了
that I won't be giving a concession speech.
先生  您不觉得这样看起来像在逃避
Sir... don't you think that might look like you're running from--
我刚刚输了我的家乡
I just lost my home state.
我不想再折腾我自己了
I'm not gonna rake myself over the coals.
密查姆
Meechum?
我不能排除任何人
I'm not ruling anyone out.
先生
Sir?
我把银行保险箱拿来了
I brought the safety deposit box for you.
放下吧
You can put it down.
-密查姆  -是  先生
- Meechum. - Yes, sir?
我有没有给过你任何伤害我的理由
Have I given you any reason to hurt me?
伤害您  先生
Hurt you, sir?
我有没有过对不起你的时候
Have I done you wrong in any way?
抱歉  先生  我不明白
I'm sorry, sir, I don't understand.
看着我的眼睛  密查姆
Look me in the eyes, Meechum.
-先生  -密查姆
- Sir... - Meechum, shh.
您还好吗  先生
Are you all right, sir?
不怎么样
I've been better.
我还在执勤
I'm still on duty.
有什么...
Is there...
我能做的吗
anything I can do?
你可以出去帮我多投些票
You could go out and stuff some ballot boxes for me.
-您能缓过来的  -真能就好了
- You'll bounce back from this. - I sure hope I can.
我之前被国会警察...
Uh, when I got fired...
开除以后
from the Capitol Police...
我知道这不能相提并论  但是...
I mean, I know it doesn't compare, but...
我特别难过
I felt pretty bad.
我以为我的职业生涯终结了
I thought my career was over.
然后您扭转了一切
Then you turned everything around.
在选举中  没有第二次机会
You don't get second chances in elections.
我知道
I know.
但还有很多场初选
But there's a lot of primaries ahead.
还没有结束  您能过这一关的
All I'm saying is it's not over. You'll get through this.
-抱歉  听起来一定很蠢  -没有
- I'm sorry, that must sound so stupid. - No, it doesn't.
我很感激
I appreciate it.
我去外面车队那里了  有事情叫我
I'll be out by the motorcade, sir, if you need anything.
谢谢  密查姆
Thank you, Meechum.
我就知道  但是不愿相信
I knew it, but I didn't wanna believe it.
只是个伤口罢了
It's only a wound.
并不致命
It's not fatal.
我的家乡  克莱尔
My home state, Claire.
坐
Have a seat.
我终结了你的竞选  所以你以牙还牙
I end your race so you end mine?
-弗兰西斯让我解释  -赌气  报复
- Let me explain, Francis. - Spite, revenge!
坐下吧  我们得谈谈
Please, sit down. We need to talk.
现在生气也没用
Nothing is going to come from anger right now.
昨晚聊天的时候  你说这座房子是宫殿
Last night when we were talking, you called this house a palace.
这是我们开始的地方
This is where we began.
你还记得我母亲差点离开了爸爸
And do you remember when my mother almost left Daddy
就因为他资助了你的竞选吗
because he funded your campaign?
她就有那么讨厌你
That's how much she hated you.
但我当时不在意
But I didn't care,
因为我看到了你的潜质  我看到了未来
because I saw something. I saw a future.
我们的未来
Our future.
你开始摧毁一切以前  我们本还有未来
We had a future until you started destroying it.
要不你不会听的
Well, you wouldn't have listened otherwise.
我一直都听你的
I always listen to you.
只在我说了你想听的的时候
Only when it's what you want to hear.
好吧  克莱尔  我现在在听
Well, all right, Claire. I'm listening now.
你有什么话这么想说
What is it you so desperately needed to say?
三十年来我们从没输过竞选
We've never lost a race in 30 years.
我们从这里开始  所向披靡
We started here and we've always won.
你我一起
You and I, together.
但你要输了  弗兰西斯
But you are losing, Francis.
人们承受不起高价油
People are getting killed at the gas pumps.
《美国就业法案》不及预期
America Works is falling flat.
你的竞选经理看不清现在的形势
Your campaign manager is ten years behind ten years ago.
你没有可靠的竞选伙伴
You don't have a viable running mate.
我们都清楚不能是唐纳德·布莱斯
We both know it can't be Donald Blythe.
当然不能
Well, of course not.
但我连名都提不上
But I have to win the goddamn nomination
-还考虑什么输赢  -就算我没这么做
- before I can start worrying about winning. - Even if I hadn't done what I did,
你的竞选也问题重重
your race is in real trouble.
你需要我  弗兰西斯
You need me, Francis.
我的支持率比你高
My approvals are higher than yours.
我能帮你赢下德州
I can help you win Texas.
没错  所以我不希望你在达拉斯竞选
Exactly. Which is why I didn't want you running in Dallas.
我需要你在我身旁
I need you at my side.
没错  但是以另一种方式
Yes, but in a different way.
什么方式
Different how?
我们能相互扶持  让彼此更强  对吧
We make each other stronger, can we agree to that?
那得步调协调  但现在不是这样
When it's working, but it's not working.
我们能协调好
We can make it work.
我们能实现当初结婚时我看到的未来
We can accomplish that future I saw when we first got married.
我们作为伙伴  真正的伙伴
It was us, as partners, real partners.
我们再一起竞选吧
Let's run together, again.
不只作为夫妻
Not just as husband and wife.
你不是指...
You don't mean...
没错
Yes.
我很担心你  克莱尔
I'm worried about you, Claire.
你在说疯话  你被自负蒙蔽了
You're not making any sense. You've let your ego get in the way--
我一直都是你的竞选伙伴
I've always been your running mate.
-你只是不愿承认  -当我的副总统吗
- You just didn't wanna see it. - As my vice president?
-天啊  你知道这...  -我反复考虑过了
- Jesus. Do you have any idea--  - I've put a lot of thought into this.
你肯定没想清楚
You can't have thought it through.
-如果你真想透彻了  -她没经验
- Because if you did, you'd come up - She has no experience.
-就能想到千万个理由  -她从没竞选过
- with a million reasons-- - She's never run for anything.
无子  任人唯亲  傲慢  我都考虑过了
No children, nepotism, arrogance, I've run through them all.
没我你赢不了
You can't win without me.
我宁愿选懦弱的唐纳德·布莱斯当我副总统
I would rather have a spineless Donald Blythe as my vice president
也强过一个没当选过公职的女人
than a woman who's never held elected office.
你要输给一个没当选过公职的女人了
You're losing to a woman who's never held elected office.
你不配
You don't deserve it.
你没尝过一无所有的滋味
You have no idea what it means to have nothing.
你不重视我们的成就
You don't value what we have achieved.
我这辈子事事都要靠自己努力争取
I have had to fight for everything my entire life.
你知道我为什么留着这张照片吗
Do you know why I kept this?
你知道吗
Do you know?
因为这是我唯一一次为我父亲骄傲
Because it's the one time I was proud of my father.
因为这个男人在这一刻  虽然可鄙
Because this man, in this moment, as despicable as it was,
在为生存而奋斗
is fighting to survive.
他不惜一切
He is doing whatever it took.
有没有你  我也会这样
And so will I, with or without you.
所以我不要跟你谈下去了
So no, I will not have this conversation.
我不会再纵容你了
I will not indulge you any further.
你得放弃
You have to let this go.
我可以参与你的竞选  也可以结束你的竞选
I can be a part of your campaign, or I can end it.
我也会不惜一切  就像你父亲那样
I'll do whatever it takes, too. Just like your father.
但我不会放弃
But I will not let this go.
给我备辆车去格林维尔机场
I'll need a car to the Greenville Airport.
去达拉斯  没错
To Dallas, yes.